http://karolfulfillmentservices.com/privacy.php

PRIVACY POLICY
Karol Fulfillment’s website uses Google Analytics to collect information about website traffic. No personally identifiable information is collected during this process. Personally identifiable information is captured only when you contact us and willingly disclose that information. We use information submitted by you to communicate with you, provide you with customer service and process your transactions. If we email you promotional information, we may receive a confirmation when you open or click on the content in those emails. If you do not wish to receive such emails from us, you can easily unsubscribe from a link that's included in every email.
Unless specifically authorized by you, Karol Fulfillment does not provide personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may share your personally identifiable information with companies that provide support services or help market our services. Although these companies may need information about you in order to perform their duties, they are not authorized to use it for any other purpose. We may share personally identifiable information and other data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Karol Fulfillment.
If Karol Fulfillment is merged, acquired, or sold, or if some or all of our assets or equity are transferred, we may disclose or transfer personally identifiable information and other data in connection with the associated transactions. We may also provide information to a third party in response to a subpoena or to otherwise comply with the law.
